Eat. Sleep. Rave. Repeat.
XOXO is a music, drama film directed by Christopher Louie.
XOXO follows six strangers whose lives collide in one
frenetic, dream-chasing, hopelessly romantic night.
Krystal, played by Sarah Hyland.
Shannie, played by Hayley Kiyoko.
Neil, played by Chris D'Elia.
Ethan, played by Graham Phillips.
Chopper, played by LaMonica Garrett.
DJ Avilo, played by Ryan Hansen.
XOXO is a 2016 American drama film directed by Christopher Louie and starring Sarah Hyland, Graham
Phillips, Brett DelBuono, Hayley Kiyoko, Colin Woodell, Ryan Hansen, Ione Skye, and Chris D'Elia.
It is based on a story by Louie and is written by Dylan Meyer.
It was produced by Joe Russell, Christopher
Louie, Daniel Shafer and Max Leitman.
The film was released on Netflix on August 26, 2016.
It received mixed reviews.
The film explores themes of rave, techno, festival.
The tone is emotional.